Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride away!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's dreaming
where we should be going. Go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the wave.
We're all together as well.
So let's escape when it's done.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one. Go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
Running forever. Open the map inside your
heart and see. No matter where we end up,
Our minds will never give up. There's
a fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
All right, is everybody ready? Yeah!
We'll sneak into the
underground port by taking
the hidden passage from
our current location.
We should avoid conflict and
aim only for our target, Sugar!
She may seem harmless,
but she's quite deadly.
All we have to do is knock her out.
Then every toy in the kingdom
will become human once more! Yeah!
But the path forward is kind of, uh...
narrow.
It's gonna be a tight squeeze. I think.
Um, Frawland, right.
Just disconnect your arms
and your shoulders, maybe?
Yeah, right!
Hey, I'm sure that passage of yours
is real super, but Meeland can't fit!
Sorry, we just didn't build it for
big people or for extra big people.
You'll have to enter through
the toy house instead.
The toy house is located at the base of
the plateau that the palace is built on.
That's where the toys must
return to every night.
Humans aren't allowed to enter.
I see and you call it a house cuz the toys
live there No, it's a house in name only.
There are no beds for sleeping there
Only a hidden passage leading
downward to the port. What for?
Without a moment's rest,
the toys are forced on the ground every
night and slave away
until the morning comes.
So those toys in the city have to put on a
show all day after slaving away all night?
The poor things!
What a cruel fate!
Well, anyway,
so you said Frohling could get to the
Smile Factory through the toy house?
Correct.
There are four ways in.
However, all of them are tightly guarded.
That suits me just fine, little buddy.
Huh?
See, while I'm there, I'll
raise some hell for you.
Huh?
But aren't we sneaking in?
You're sneaking in.
That's the point.
Get it? Huh?
While I'm drawing everyone's attention,
you slip it all quiet-like
and take down sugar.
Huh? Who is that weirdo?
Where are his pants?
What's wrong with his head?
Maybe he's just crazy.
He's got a triple chin too.
Wait a second—we know this guy!
It's Cyborg Franky from the Straw Hats.
hats
Oh no, senor, you can't just bite
right into a tomato like that.
You need a napkin, it's too juicy.
Oh, senor!
You're so hard-boiled!
Get off of me, ladies.
That's enough.
You'd be better off
with a man your own age.
But we, like you, don't
turn us away, senor!
Sorry, I don't...
...like kids.
Oh, senor!
Please let us stay, senor! Please!
Senor!
What the?
Get a load of that pervert.
You're one to talk! Attention!
This is the east entrance
to the toy house reporting.
We're under enemy attack.
Knock, knock! Let me hit!
Weapons left!
Shoot him!
It's a member of the Straw Hats!
Cyborg Franky is here!
What did I tell you?
Those guys are out of control.
This nation is affiliated
with the world government.
It's your job to help me.
The party's starting.
Toy house, huh?
Sounds messy.
Don't worry, we already
know their objective.
The Smile Factory!
And you know what happens
if they make it that far?
We turn them all into toys.
That sound good to you?
They're so clueless, dummies.
You're our secret.
They sure will be surprised, won't they?
I guess so. Oh, oh.
We're almost at the train port. Get ready.
Commander, it's Frawlind.
He's wreaking havoc at the
toy house, just as promised.
Got it.
See, while I'm there,
I'll go race some hell for you.
I hope he stays safe.
He'll be fine.
Frawlind's a super cyborg
after all. Be that as it may,
I just received word that
four of the family executives
have been sent to guard
the toyhouse. Is that bad.
They are fearsome skilled fighters
All members of the Diamante army.
They're the biggest stars in
the whole Coliseum In fact,
in all the matches that they fought,
they've never lost once and that
goes for all four of them, too.
It's a heck of a record!
Aren't the fighters in the Coliseum
supposed to be tough though?
They are which means one thing.
So just how many tough guys are we
up against? There's ten executives.
each leading two thousand men spread
out across the entire kingdom?
Then there's three top executives
that stand above even them,
each of the three command their
own army with unique features.
First the treble army members
all have special abilities.
like Sugar,
Violet,
and Geola.
Next, there's the Diamante Army,
consisting of strong fighters
like Lao-Gi, Mokweiss,
Senor Pink and Dellinger.
And then there's Peacock
with his commando unit.
He commands Gladius,
Buffalo, and Baby Five.
Yeah, we fought with those last two
before we got here, and they were tough.
There's two more who
are operating overseas.
Another top exec, Vergo.
And a regular exec, Monet.
So we don't have to face the team
with all the strong fighters.
That's on Franky!
That team may be the
most deadly of them all.
Why did you have to tell me that?
Oh, no!
I'm sorry, Usalind!
Thank you. My pleasure.
Are you ready?
We're in the enemy base.
The factory is right over there.
Well, that would explain
all the factory noise.
That must be coming from above, right?
Hey, who dropped this box?
Pull it together.
Nah, it fell on top of a toy.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep working.
Just let me see my family. Your family?
The only thing you're going
to see is the scrap heap.
Now take them away.
Anything but that.
I can still make my quota. Have mercy.
Over here.
Robin, did you? Shh.
Just look.
We'll just do business with someone else.
You know that is a rotten deal.
I'd clean your clock
if it wasn't for Joker.
What the hell is this place?
They've got a whole port city down here!
To be
continued...
He stalks the battlefield like a ghost.
No, like a grim reaper.
Everything that I did, it was
all for the sake of my country.
A land that I once loved.
Can you say the same?
Get out of Dressrosa!
The people truly seem to despise you.
It must be suffocating living
under the weight of their contempt.
I don't care how hard it is.
I don't care how much they hate me.
All I want is to live together
with Soldier in Peace!
Such a beautiful, such
a detestable display!
Anyway, let's hear it for the final
30 competitors here in Block D!
Another man is down forever, an animal!
The lion Agyo is truly the king of beasts,
making the Coliseum run red with
the blood of his countless victims.
And yet even a king must kneel
before the might of Orlumbus' whip!
He's strong!
Yeah, you got this!
Our strongest competitors
are still in the game!
But we may see an upset
from an unknown fighter!
At any rate, only one can advance!
They've all got their sights on Rebecca!
Who's going to take her head?
Soldier, I don't know where you are
right now, but please don't die.
That's all I ask.
What?
What do you mean?
The soldier went on ahead.
He's the leader.
While we're down here, he'll be busy
preparing for the next leg of the operation.
Once we take out Sugar, Doflamingo will
be vulnerable to a surprise attack.
So he's headed to the palace with a
team of Tantata to assassinate him.
Good luck, Commander.
But we'll be fine because we
have a legendary hero like you.
Please take command of Operation
SOP and do battle with Sugar!
Only you can lead us to victory! What?
Don't give me the most important job!
Are you nuts?
This is where we are right now.
All the bridges in this area move.
Now take a look at that
building in the distance.
The one that looks like a sea anemone.
That's the executive tower.
Where our target sugar will be waiting.
Stop screwing around and get back to work.
You think I don't see you?
They found us!
We're done for!
Wait a minute.
What ship do you work on?
I'm just an innocent passerby, sir.
Feel free to ignore me.
We don't allow when you want to get
off the ship, except the brokers.
Everyone knows that now in hell.
Cover!
Naked and buried, huh?
Here, Usalin.
Robalin, your disguises.
Nice one! Wow!
You really think fast.
Pretending you were scared gave
us the perfect chance to attack.
Hey, are all of you guys that strong?
That attack really packed a punch.
That's pretty average for us.
Of course, that's nothing
compared to your power.
people from Nolan's
bloodline can take down
sea kings are great. Really
think I'm some kind of
super-powered monster
don't they you know what
fine I think I have a
plan maybe I can pull this
Off without fighting. All
right, listen to Zeland.
I am taking command of
this operation our target
is a little girl right
so we're not gonna fight
her we're gonna scare her
out of our wits Yes, sir!
Yeah, actually, uh...
Lead the way, my brave friends!
To the tower! Straight ahead!
Everyone, get in the lift!
There's an intruder at the toy house!
It's one of the straw hat pirates, Franky.
The report says he's at the east
entrance fighting with Senor Pink.
He's aiming for the factory on this floor
Good luck out there if we take him out.
We should get a nice bonus
Holy crap like how much well
his bounty is pretty high
At this rate, we'll be stuck
going up and down in here forever.
Let's take over the lift.
Wait here for now.
I'm seizing this lift.
Don't move.
I know you.
The soldier from the Coliseum.
How'd you get in here?
Where'd he go? Over here.
Little punk.
You're too slow!
Too slow!
That's domestic violence!
It's child abuse!
You were supposed to dodge!
If it was up to me, I
wouldn't hit you at all!
Then don't follow through with your swing!
You need a sense of danger
to improve yourself!
Now focus! Once again!
Human instinct is powerful.
You're much stronger than this.
Look within yourself.
Show me the strength of humanity.
What would you know
about that? You're a toy.
And you're still too slow.
I don't want to fight.
I don't want to practice anymore.
Why can't you keep protecting me?
I'm nothing but a toy,
beaten by the wind and rain.
My body rusts.
I don't know how long I can continue.
Rebecca, stand up.
Become strong.
This body is not meant to fight.
Perhaps toys only exist to
be broken from the start.
Before the children who play
with them become adults.
Damn it!
Forgive me, Rebecca.
It seems I failed you as a father.
All I could teach you is how to fight.
Nobody warned me.
This guy was so strong.
What is a toy like you even want?
Why are you fighting us?
I'm here because I want a kingdom at
peace, where my child can live happily.
To that end, I shall fight for King Rick.
King Rick?
What the hell are you saying?
You've lost your mind!
I will lay my life on the line.
I must see this mission through.
Impressive speed.
Yeah, no joke!
I must have blinked and missed it.
So it seems the rumors are true.
I'm speechless, folks.
Just like that, the
whole ring is out cold.
All of the top contenders have
been felled in an instant!
No one, no one is left standing!
I've never seen anything like it!
The match has ended in an instant,
but there's no winner to speak of!
Wait!
Do you see that?
In the smoke, one fighter begins to rise!
Oh, my God.